http://www.swingtowns.com/privacy.html

Login
swingTowns
SwingTowns.comPrivacy PolicyLast Updated: June 6, 2019IntroductionWelcome to Street Ink Corp.’s privacy policy.Street Ink respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal data. This privacy policy will inform you as to how we look after your personal data when you visit our website (regardless of where you visit it from) and tell you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.This privacy policy is provided in a layered format so you can click through to the specific areas set out below. Please also use the Glossary to understand the meaning of some of the terms used in this privacy policy.Important Information and Who We AreThe Data We Collect About YouHow Is Your Personal Data CollectedHow We Use Your Personal DataDisclosures of Your Personal DataInternational TransfersData SecurityData RetentionDo Not Track PolicyYour California Privacy RightsYour Canadian Privacy RightsYour Legal RightsGlossary1.        Important information and who we arePurpose of this privacy policyThis privacy policy aims to give you information on how Street Ink collects and processes your personal data through your use of this website, including any data you may provide through this website when you sign up.This website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.It is important that you read this privacy policy together with any other privacy policy or fair processing policy we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy policy supplements other notices and privacy policies and is not intended to override them.ControllerStreet Ink Corporation is the controller and responsible for your personal data (collectively referred to as “Street Ink,” “we,” “us,” or “our” in this privacy policy).We have appointed a data privacy manager who is responsible for overseeing questions in relation to this privacy policy. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, please contact the data privacy manager using the details set out below.Contact detailsIf you have any questions about this privacy policy or our privacy practices, please contact our data privacy manager in the following ways:Full name of legal entity: Street Ink CorporationEmail address: privacy@swingtowns.comPostal address: 800 Belle Terre Parkway #200-131, Palm Coast, Florida 32164If you reside in the UK, you have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues (www.ico.org.uk). If you reside within the EEA, you have the right to make a complaint at any time to the appropriate supervisory authority for your country of residence. See http://ec.europa.eu for these details. If you reside outside the EEA, we will apply your legal rights as applicable to the data laws in the jurisdiction you are in.We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach your supervisory authority so please contact us in the first instance.Changes to the privacy policy and your duty to inform us of changesWe keep our privacy policy under regular review. This version was last updated on August 21, 2018. Historic versions can be obtained by contacting us.It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal data changes during your relationship with us.Third-party linksThis website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins, and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our website, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit.2.        The data we collect about youPersonal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data).We may collect, use, store, and transfer different kinds of personal data about you which we have grouped together as follows:Identity Data includes first name and last name (for affiliates only), nickname, username or similar identifier, marital/relationship status, date of birth, and gender.Contact Data includes billing address, email address, and telephone number (for affiliates only).Financial Data includes bank account details.Transaction Data includes details about payments to and from you and other details of services you have purchased from us.Technical Data includes internet protocol (IP) address, cookie ID, affiliate ID, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform, and other technology on the devices you use to access this website.Profile Data includes your username and password, purchases or orders made by you, your interests, preferences, pictures (please remember that photographs that you post on your profile may reveal information about yourself as well), feedback, and survey responses. Some of the information you choose to provide us may be considered “special” or “sensitive” in certain jurisdictions, for example your sex life and sexual orientation. By choosing to provide this information, you consent to our processing of that information.Usage Data includes information about how you use our website, products, and services, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URLs); clickstream to, through, and from our website (including date and time); information you viewed or searched for; page response times; download errors; length of visits to certain pages; page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs); and methods used to browse away from the page.Marketing and Communications Data includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.We also collect, use, and share Aggregated Data such as statistical or demographic data for any purpose. Aggregated Data could be derived from your personal data but is not considered personal data in law as this data will not directly or indirectly reveal your identity. For example, we may aggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of users accessing a specific website feature. However, if we combine or connect Aggregated Data with your personal data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this privacy policy.We collect Special Categories of Personal Data about your sex life and sexual orientation only. We do not collect any information about criminal convictions and offenses.If you fail to provide personal dataWhere we need to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of a contract we have with you and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have or are trying to enter into with you (for example, to provide you with goods or services). In this case, we may have to cancel a product or service you have with us, but we will notify you if this is the case at the time.3.        How is your personal data collected?We use different methods to collect data from and about you, including through:Direct interactions. You may give us your Identity, Contact, Financial, and Special Categories of Personal Data by filling in forms or by corresponding with us by email or otherwise. This includes personal data you provide when you:create an account on our website;request marketing to be sent to you;enter a competition, promotion, or survey; orgive us feedback or contact us.Automated technologies or interactions. As you interact with our website, we will automatically collect Technical and Usage Data about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies, server logs, and other similar technologies. We may also receive Technical and Usage Data about you if you visit other websites employing our cookies. Please see our cookie policy for further details.Third parties or publicly available sources. We will receive personal data about you from various third parties as set out below:Technical Data from the following parties:analytics providers such as Google based outside the EU;advertising networks based outside the EU; andsearch information providers such as Google based outside the EU.Contact, Financial, and Transaction Data from providers of technical, payment, and delivery services such as CCBill based outside the EU.Identity and Contact Data from publicly available sources on the Internet.4.        How we use your personal dataWe will only use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you.Where you have given consent for us to use your sensitive personal data provide certain services. (You may withdraw your consent for some uses of the data at any time by contacting us.)Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.Where we need to comply with a legal obligation.Click here to find out more about the types of lawful basis that we will rely on to process your personal data.Generally, we do not rely on consent as a legal basis for processing your personal data although we will get your consent before collecting sensitive personal data or sending third-party direct marketing communications to you via email. You have the right to withdraw consent to marketing at any time by contacting us.Purposes for which we will use your personal dataWe have set out below, in a table format, a description of all the ways we plan to use your personal data, and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate.Note that we may process your personal data for more than one lawful ground depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data. Please contact us if you need details about the specific legal ground we are relying on to process your personal data where more than one ground has been set out in the table below.Purpose/ActivityType of dataLawful basis for processing including basis of legitimate interestTo register you as a new customer or affiliate(a) Identity(b) Contact(c) Financial(d) Profile(a) Performance of a contract with you(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation(c) With your explicit consent in the case of sensitive personal dataTo provide the services to you, including:(a) Maintaining a profile, answering questions, and providing information about yourself(b) Analyzing your personal data to match you with other users(c) Allowing you to communicate with other users to make a match(d) Enabling you to purchase subscriptions to enhance your opportunities to make a match with other users(a) Identity(b) Contact(c) Financial(d) Transaction(e) Profile(f) Marketing and Communications(a) Performance of a contract with you(b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to improve our service)(c) With your consent in the case of sensitive personal dataTo manage our relationship with you which will include:(a) Notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy policy(b) Communicate with you(a) Identity(b) Contact(c) Transaction(d) Profile(e) Usage(f) Marketing and Communications(a) Performance of a contract with you(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation(c) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated)To enable you to partake in a prize draw, competition, or complete a survey(a) Identity(b) Contact(c) Profile(d) Usage(e) Marketing and Communications(a) Performance of a contract with you(b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, and grow our business)To administer and protect our business and this website (including security, fraud, troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting, and hosting of data)(a) Identity(b) Contact(c) Technical(d) Profile(e) Usage(f) Marketing and Communications(a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud, and in the context of a business reorganization or group restructuring exercise)(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligationTo deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you(a) Identity(b) Contact(c) Profile(d) Usage(e) Marketing and Communications(f) TechnicalNecessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business, and to inform our marketing strategy)To use data analytics to improve our website, products/services, marketing, customer relationships, and experiences(a) Technical(b) Profile(c) UsageNecessary for our legitimate interests (to define types of customers for our products and services, to keep our website updated and relevant, to develop our business, and to inform our marketing strategy)To make suggestions and recommendations to you about goods or services that may be of interest to you(a) Identity(b) Contact(c) Technical(d) Usage(e) Profile(f) Marketing and CommunicationsNecessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and grow our business)MarketingWe strive to provide you with choices regarding certain personal data uses, particularly around marketing and advertising. We have established the following personal data control mechanisms:Promotional offers from usWe may use your Identity, Contact, Technical, Usage, and Profile Data to form a view on what we think you may want or need, or what may be of interest to you. This is how we decide which products, services, and offers may be relevant for you (we call this marketing).You will receive marketing communications from us if you have requested information from us or signed up for an affiliate account and, in each case, you have not opted out of receiving that marketing.Third-party marketingWe will get your express opt-in consent before we share your personal data with any third party for marketing purposes.Opting outYou can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by logging into the website and checking or unchecking relevant boxes to adjust your marketing preferences, by following the opt-out links on any marketing messages sent to you, or by contacting us at any time.Where you opt out of receiving these marketing messages, this will not apply to personal data provided to us as a result of other transactions.CookiesYou can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when websites set or access cookies. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this website may become inaccessible or not function properly. For more information about the cookies we use, please see our cookie policy.Change of purposeWe will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you wish to get an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us.If we need to use your personal data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.Please note that we may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.5.        Disclosures of your personal dataOur service allows you to share information about yourself with other individuals and other companies, including other users and other potential users of the service or other products or services offered by us. Consider your own privacy and personal safety when sharing your information with anyone, including information you share through your profile.We may share your personal data with the parties set out below for the purposes stated in the table (Purposes for which we will use your personal data) above.External Third Parties as set out in the Glossary.Third parties to whom we may choose to sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets. Alternatively, we may seek to acquire other businesses or merge with them. If a change happens to our business, then the new owners may use your personal data in the same way as set out in this privacy policy.We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.6.        International transfersThe personal data we collect may be transferred to, and processed and stored in, countries outside of the jurisdiction you are in where we and our third-party service providers have operations. If you are located in the European Economic Area (EEA), your personal data may be processed outside of the EEA, including, for example, in the United States, so processing of your personal data will involve a transfer of data outside the EEA.Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it by ensuring at least one of the following safeguards is implemented:We will only transfer your personal data to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission. For further details, see European Commission: Adequacy of the protection of personal data in non-EU countries.Where we use certain service providers, we may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe. For further details, see European Commission: Model contracts for the transfer of personal data to third countries.Where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them if they are part of the Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to personal data shared between Europe and the US. For further details, see European Commission: EU–US Privacy Shield.Please contact us if you want further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your personal data out of the EEA.7.        Data securityWe have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used, or accessed in an unauthorized way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors, and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.We will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our services, but given that no information transmitted over the Internet can be guaranteed 100% secure, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and hence accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.8.        Data retentionHow long will you use my personal data for?We will only retain your personal data for as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, regulatory, tax, accounting, or reporting requirements. We may retain your personal data for a longer period in the event of a complaint or if we reasonably believe there is a prospect of litigation in respect to our relationship with you.To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal, regulatory, tax, accounting, or other requirements.By law we have to keep basic information about our customers (including Contact, Identity, Financial, and Transaction Data) for seven years after they cease being customers for tax purposes.In some circumstances you can ask us to delete your data: see your legal rights below for further information.In some circumstances we will anonymize your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.9.        Do Not Track policyDo Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that you can set in your browser. DNT is a way for you to inform websites and services that you do not want certain information about your webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. We are committed to providing you with meaningful choices about the information we collect and that is why we provide you the ability to opt out. But we do not recognize or respond to any DNT signals as the Internet industry works toward defining exactly what DNT means, what it means to comply with DNT, and a common approach to responding to DNT. For more information, visit www.allaboutdnt.com.10.        Your California privacy rightsIf you are a California resident, you are granted specific rights regarding access to your personal data. California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the name and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal data in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided above.11.        Your Canadian privacy rightsWe comply with Canadian Federal and Provincial privacy laws and regulations, including the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act.We will only use your personal information for the purposes intended and as detailed in this policy unless we have obtained your consent to use it for other purposes.Residents of Canada are notified that the personal data they provide to Street Ink is stored in its databases outside of Canada, including in the United States, and may be subject to disclosure to authorized law enforcement or government agencies in response to lawful demand under the laws of that country. You may withdraw your consent to our personal data collection, use, or disclosure, subject to legal and contractual restrictions.You have the right to complain about our personal data handling practices.If you need to contact us about your personal data or believe that we have violated your privacy rights, please contact us at privacy@swingtowns.com. You may visit www.priv.gc.ca for more information about your privacy rights.12.        Your legal rightsUnder certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data. Please click on the links below to find out more about these rights:Request access to your personal data.Request correction of your personal data.Request erasure of your personal data.Object to processing of your personal data.Request restriction of processing your personal data.Request transfer of your personal data.Right to withdraw consent.If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please contact us.No fee usually requiredYou will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive, or excessive. Alternatively, we could refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.What we may need from youWe may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.Time limit to respondWe try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it could take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.13.        GlossaryLawful BasisLegitimate Interest means the interest of our business in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best service/product and the best and most secure experience. We make sure we consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative) and your rights before we process your personal data for our legitimate interests. We do not use your personal data for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law). You can obtain further information about how we assess our legitimate interests against any potential impact on you in respect of specific activities by contacting us.Performance of Contract means processing your data where it is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or to take steps at your request before entering into such a contract.Comply with a legal obligation means processing your personal data where it is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation that we are subject to.Third PartiesExternal Third PartiesCompliance with Laws. We may disclose your information where we are legally required to do so to comply with applicable law, government requests, a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements).Vital Interests and Legal Rights. We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of our policies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.Vendors, Consultants, and Other Third-Party Service Providers. We may share your data with third-party vendors, service providers, contractors, or agents who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to that information to do that work. Examples include: payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service, and marketing efforts. We may allow selected third parties to use tracking technology on the Website, which will enable them to collect data about how you interact with the Website over time. This information may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the website (you can read more about how Google uses your personal data here: https://policies.google.com/privacy). You can also optout of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. We also use AddThis to collect information from visitors of our website. You can easily opt out of interest-based advertising facilitated by AddThis at any time using the AddThis opt out. You can also opt out at http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/, and http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/. For more information about AddThis’s privacy practices, see http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/. Advertising Networks. We may share your personal data with advertising networks and technology companies that measure advertising performance and attribution.Affiliates. We may share your information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this privacy policy.Your Legal RightsYou have the right to:Request access to your personal data (commonly known as a “data subject access request”). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.Request correction of the personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.Request erasure of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal data where you have successfully exercised your right to object to processing (see below), where we may have processed your information unlawfully, or where we are required to erase your personal data to comply with local law. Note, however, that we may not always be able to comply with your request of erasure for specific legal reasons which will be notified to you, if applicable, at the time of your request.Object to processing of your personal data where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground as you feel it impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes. In some cases, we may demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate grounds to process your information which override your rights and freedoms.Request restriction of processing of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your personal data in the following scenarios:If you want us to establish the data’s accuracy.Where our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it.Where you need us to hold the data even if we no longer require it as you need it to establish, exercise, or defend legal claims.You have objected to our use of your data but we need to verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it.Request the transfer of your personal data to you or to a third party. We will provide to you, or a third party you have chosen, your personal data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.Withdraw consent at any time where we are relying on consent to process your personal data. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you. We will advise you if this is the case at the time you withdraw your consent.
